Guide to the Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects, LLC, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project Records, 1965-2010
  - Haupt Residence, 1977
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 652)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 652)
  - Arango Apartment, 1981
    Job number: 19-8107
    Client: Arango
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 661–662, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 662)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 662)
  - Garey Residence, 1988
    Job number: 19-8309
    Job location: Kent, CT
    Client: Garey
    - Background and Reports (Box 451)
    - Design Development (Box 451)
    - Correspondence (Box 451)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 671)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 451, Box 672, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 671–673)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 672)
  - Dartmouth College John W. Berry Sports Center, 1988
    Job number: 19-8328
    Job location: Hanover, NH
    Client: Dartmouth College
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 681–682)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 683–685, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 684–687)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 688–690)
  - Cornell Uni. College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1992
    Job number: 19-8401
    Job location: Ithica, NY
    Client: Cornell University
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 701)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 702–703, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 704–708)
  - Cornell Uni. Fieldhouse and Basketball Arena, 1989
    Job number: 19-8509
    - Background and Reports (Box 711)
    - Design Development (Box 711)
    - Correspondence (Box 711)
    - Specifications (Box 711)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 711)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 712, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 713–715)
  - Cornell Uni. Theory Center at the College of Engineering, 1990
    Job number: 19-8803
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 721)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 722)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 723–726)
  - 1585 Broadway Office Tower, 1989
    Job number: 19-8518
    Client: Salmon Equities
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 731, Box 733–734, Box 742–743, Box 745–746, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 732–733, Box 735–741, Box 744)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 742–743)
  - Morgan Stanley World Headquarters, Including 1585 Broadway Office Tower, 1990
    Job number: 19-9401
    Client: 1585 Broadway / Morgan Stanley
    - Background and Reports (Box 751)
    - Correspondence (Box 751)
    - Specifications (Box 751)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 751, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 752)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 751–753, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 754)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 755)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 753)
  - Disney Planned Residential Community
    Job number: 19-8720
    Job location: Lake Bueno Vista, FL
    Project type: Hospitality/Corporate
    Client: Walt Disney World
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 761)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 761–762, Box 2073)
  - Walt Disney World Resort Convention Exhibition Center / "Meeting Facility", 1992
    Job number: 19-8912
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 772)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 771–774, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 771, Box 775)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 775)
  - Disney Contemporary Resort, 1991
    Job number: 19-8933
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 781)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 781)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 782–784)
  - Walt Disney World: Contemporary Disney Vacation Club (DVC)
    Job number: 20-0517
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 787)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 785–787)
  - Walt Disney World Bonnet Creek Golf Clubhouse, 1992
    Job number: 19-9015
    Project type: Hospitality
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 791)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 792)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 793–794)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 795)
  - Disney Contemporary Resort Hospitality Suites & Redevelopment, 1998
    Job number: 19-9814
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 801)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 801)
  - Disney Garden Wing Connector/Contemporary Resort Hotel, 1998
    Job number: 19-9211
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 811)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 811)
  - Apartment 10A, 1988
    Job number: 19-8811
    - Correspondence (Box 451)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 821)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 451, Box 822, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 821)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 821–822)
  - Sobel Apartment / Apartment 10 W (Originally Koppelman Apartment), 1992
    Job number: 19-8915
    Client: Koppelman/Sobel Residence
    - Background and Reports (Box 831)
    - Correspondence (Box 831)
    - Specifications (Box 831)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 831, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 832–833, Box 836)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 831–833, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 835–836)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 834, Box 837, Box 839)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 838)
  - Euro-Disney Golf Clubhouse, 1993
    Job number: 19-9011
    Job location: Marne-la-Vallee, France
    Client: Euro-Disney
    - Background and Reports (Box 841)
    - Correspondence (Box 841)
    - Specifications (Box 841)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 841)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 841, Box 843)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 841–842, Box 845, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 842, Box 845)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 843, Box 845)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 844)
  - Euro-Disney Convention Center & Hotel, 1992
    Job number: 19-9115
    - Correspondence (Box 841)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 853, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 852–855, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 851)
  - Science, Industry and Business Library (SIBL), 1996
    Job number: 19-9108
    Project type: Library
    Client: The New York Public Library
    - Background and Reports (Box 861)
    - Design Development (Box 861)
    - Correspondence (Box 861)
    - Specifications (Box 861)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 861)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 862–865, Box 882)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 861, Box 866–868, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 867, Box 869–876, Box 878–879)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 871, Box 873, Box 877, Box 880–881)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 878–879)
  - 717 Fifth Avenue, 1995
    Job number: 19-9210
    Project type: Interior/Corporate
    Client: Equitable Real Estate
    - Design Development (Box 891)
    - Correspondence (Box 891)
    - Specifications (Box 891)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 892)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 893)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 894–897)
  - 21 International Holdings, Inc., 1994
    Job number: 19-9314
    Client: 21 International Holdings
    - Background and Reports (Box 901)
    - Design Development (Box 901)
    - Correspondence (Box 901)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 901, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 901, Box 904, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 902–903, Box 905)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 904)
  - Park Avenue Residence / Apartment 5C, 1995
    Job number: 19-9410
    Client: Park Avenue ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 451)
    - Correspondence (Box 451)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 451, Box 911, Box 913, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 912)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 451, Box 914)
  - Fifth Avenue Apartment / Winnick Residence, 1999
    Job number: 19-9517
    Client: Winnick
    - Design Development (Box 921)
    - Correspondence (Box 921)
    - Specifications (Box 921)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 921, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 922, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 924)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 921, Box 923–924)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 921, Box 925)
  - Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame, 2002
    Job number: 19-9708
    Job location: Springfield, MA
    Project type: Museum/Sports
    Client: Basketball Hall of Fame
    - Background and Reports (Box 931–932)
    - Design Development (Box 931–932)
    - Correspondence (Box 931–932)
    - Specifications (Box 932–933)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 931)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 931, Box 934, Box 944)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 931, Box 934–936, Box 938, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 931, Box 935, Box 937–943, Box 945)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 946–947)
  - ICP, 2001
    Job number: 19-9718
    Client: International Center for Photography
    - Background and Reports (Box 951)
    - Design Development (Box 951)
    - Correspondence (Box 951)
    - Specifications (Box 951)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 951, Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 951)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 951, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 952–953)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 954–955)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 956)
  - Gymnasium Apartment (Center Street), 2002
    Job number: 19-9824
    Client: Gymnasium ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1961)
    - Design Development (Box 1961)
    - Correspondence (Box 961)
    - Specifications (Box 961)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 961, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 961–963)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 961, Box 964, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 966)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 962–963, Box 965–971)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 964)
  - Tangeman University Center, 2004
    Job number: 19-9906
    Client: University of Cincinnati
    - Specifications (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 981–982)
  - Steel Loft, 2002
    Job number: 19-9913
    Client: Steel
    - Design Development (Box 451)
    - Correspondence (Box 451)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 451, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 451, Box 992)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 991–992)
  - Charof Residence, 1974
    Job number: 19-7404
    Job location: Montauk, NY
    Client: Charof
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1001, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1001)
  - Vidal Sassoon Salon Corporate Offices, 1976
    Job number: 19-7411
    Client: Vidal Sassoon
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1011–1012, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1012)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1012)
  - Vidal Sassoon Salon, South Coast Plaza, 1975
    - Background and Reports (Box 1013)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1013)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1013, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1013)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1013)
  - Vidal Sassoon Salon, Rodeo Drive, 1977
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1014)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1014, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1014)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1014)
  - Vidal Sassoon Salon, Chicago, 1975
    Job location: Chicago, IL
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1015)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1015, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1015)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1015)
  - Vidal Sassoon Salon, New York, 1975
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1016)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1016)
  - Vidal Sassoon Salon, Atlanta, 1976
    Job location: Atlanta, GA
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1017)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1017, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1017)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1017)
  - Unger Apartment, 1975
    Job number: 19-7512
    Client: New York ANONYMOUS
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1021)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1021, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1021)
  - Shezan Restaurant, 1976
    Job number: 19-7514
    Client: Shezan Restaurant
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1031)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1031, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1031)
  - East Campus Student Housing & Academic Center, Columbia University, 1980
    Job number: 19-7606
    Client: Columbia University
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1041, Box 1041A, Box 1042, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1043)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1044)
  - Swid Apartment I, 1977
    Job number: 19-7614
    Client: Swid
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1051, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1051)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1051)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1051)
  - Swid Apartment II, 1983
    Job number: 19-830A
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1052, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1052)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1052)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1052)
  - Swid Guest House & Kitchen Renovation, 1990
    Job number: 19-8913
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1053)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1053)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1053–1054)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1053–1054)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1053)
  - Swid Powell Flatware, 1985
    Job number: 19-1984
    Project type: Product Design
    Client: Swid Powell Design
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1061, Box 2073)
  - Weitz Residence, 1978
    Job number: 19-7611
    Job location: Quague, NY
    Client: Weitz
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1071, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1072)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1072)
  - Benenson Residence, 1988
    Job number: 19-7615
    Job location: Rye, NY
    Client: Benenseon
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1082)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1081–1082, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1081, Box 1083)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1082)
  - Crowley Residence, 1978
    Job number: 19-7715
    Client: Crowley
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1091)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1091–1092, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1092–1093)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1095)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1094)
  - Knoll International Showroom & Office Building, Boston, 1980
    Job number: 19-7801B
    Job location: Boston, MA
    Client: Knoll International
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1101, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1101)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1101)
  - Knoll Gwathmey-Siegel Collection, 1984
    Job number: 19-7911
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1111)
  - Knoll International Showroom, Chicago, 1985
    Job number: 19-8330
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1121)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1121, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1121–1122)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1123)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1123)
  - Pence Street Family Housing, 1984
    Job number: 19-7802
    Job location: Columbus, IN
    Client: Pence Street Family Housing
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1131–1132, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1132)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1133)
  - Triangle Pacific Corporation Office Building, 1980
    Job number: 19-7903
    Job location: Dallas, TX
    Client: Triangle Pacific Corporation
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1141, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1142)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1141)
  - Viereck Residence, 1979
    Job number: 19-7927
    Client: Viereck
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1151–1152, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1152)
  - Apartment 10A, 1982
    Job number: 19-8101
    Job location: Lincoln, NE
    Client: University of Nebraska
    - Correspondence (Box 1161)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1163, Box 2072)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1161)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1163)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1162, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1164–1166)
  - Gimelstob Residence, 1991
    Job number: 19-8110
    Job location: Harding Township, NJ
    Client: Gimelstob
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1171–1173, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1174–1176)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1177)
  - Steinberg Apartment, 1982
    Job number: 19-8111
    Client: Steinberg
    - Background and Reports (Box 1181)
    - Correspondence (Box 1181)
    - Specifications (Box 1181)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1181–1182, Box 1192–1194, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1182–1184, Box 1191, Box 1193–1194)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1193, Box 1196–1197)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1184, Box 1195)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1182, Box 1191)
  - Steinberg Residence, 1989
    Job number: 19-8606/8708
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2072)
  - International Design Center: Center 1, 1983
    Job number: 19-8327
    Client: IDC NY
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1201, Box 2073)
  - International Design Center: Center 2, 1985
    Job number: 19-8303
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1211–1212, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1212)
  - International Design Center: Center 3, 1985
    Job number: 19-8506
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1221)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1222, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1222)
  - International Design Center: Center 4, 1986
    Job number: 19-8510
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1231–1232)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1233)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1233–1234)
  - Spielberg Apartment, Trump Tower, 1995
    Job number: 19-8302
    Client: Spielberg
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1241)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1241, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1241)
  - Quelle Farm, Main Residence + SP4
    Job number: 19-8422/8507
    Client: East Hampton ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1181)
    - Design Development (Box 1181)
    - Correspondence (Box 1181)
    - Specifications (Box 1181)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1181)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1181)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1181, Box 2073)
  - Quelle Farm, Main Residence